Giuliano Forghieri

in LinkedIn profile • Personal website

A dedicated, emotionally intelligent undergraduate focused on problem-solving with an analytical mind and a strong work ethic, studying **Computer Science & Engineering** at the **Delft University of Technology** in The Netherlands.

I am deeply committed to my personal and professional development as demonstrated by the substantial work experiences and extracurricular activities I have undertaken. Having co-founded a successful business at the age of 17 and because of my love for technology, I developed an ever-growing hunger for dealing with new and challenging situations, thus my strong interest in the financial markets along with computer software. **Core Competencies:**



Great attention to detail	Leadership	Personal Integrity
Eagerness for constant improvement	Strong technical skills	Resilience under pressure
Fast decision-making skills	Team player	Multilingual
A pro-active problem-solving nature	Competitive attitude	Entrepreneurship

EDUCATION AND TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES

Delft University of Technology (TU Delft)

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering

Delft, The Netherlands

2018 - 2021

- Object Oriented Programming in Java Created a text-based catalogue application using OOP principles, multithreading and sorting
- Computer Organization and Architecture
- Web & Database Technology **Created an online multiplayer chess game, awarded with 10/10 grade.**
- Algorithms and Data Structures in Java
- Discrete Mathematics for Computation

HTH Business School

The Hague, The Netherlands

Bachelor of Business Administration (interrupted)

2016 - 2017

• Co-founder of the HTH Investment Think Tank - Entrepreneurship and Finance club

Technical Skills

Prior experience in: Java, C, JavaScript, Git, GitHub, HTML, CSS, LaTeX

Beginner in: SQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Neo4J

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marriott International (Central London Office)

London, United Kingdom

Sales Intern

2017 - 2018

- Took the initiative to develop a tool which made the proposal drafting process ~15 times quicker
- Assisted the sales maximization process of 13 Marriott properties working in a team of 25 within a fast-paced environment based in central London
- Managed, analysed and consolidated extensive amounts of data into easy-to-understand financial reports

HTH Business School

The Hague, The Netherlands

Duty Manager/Student Assistant

2016 - 2017

- Facilitated the leading of 19 other students and acted as the duty manager handling both back and front office operations, the team was responsible for almost 300 guests at Skotel The Hague
- Successfully helped to increase the response rate by 10% on the National Student Survey through digital marketing

United Colours
Co-founder
Baja, Hungary
2012 – 2015

Co-founder of the United Colours event planning business & electronic music duo:

- Organized and promoted more than 25 events with the average of 500 guests per party
- Negotiated partnership agreements with club owners and venue managers
- Generated an average revenue of €7,500 per event
- Oversaw the planning and execution of an open-air event with a budget close to €10,000. Sold more than 1,000 tickets.

HOBBIES & LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Physical training and meditation with detailed nutritional planning
- Reading books on various topics (Self-mastery, investments, psychology, nutrition etc.)
- Taking online courses mainly in Finance, Programming and Mathematics

☐ English - Fluent ☐ Italian - Proficient ☐ German - Basic ☐ Hungarian - Fl	uer	ıt
---	-----	----